PERSONAL DETAILS

Name: Jose Luis Jimenez Reid

Address: Greenwich NSW, 2065

Contact Number: 0467323897 (Mobile)

Email: j.jimenezreid@cqumail.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE

To begin a career as a software developer in modern technology focusing on a mobile application. I graduated in November 2019 of my university studies in Information Technology at Central Queensland University. General engineering courses in Mathematics and Sciences has been performed to scientific problem-solving. High performance in studies having an High-Distinction in Grade point average (GPA) and achieving a high programming skill level.

EDUCATION

2016 to 2019 **Bachelor of Information Technology**

CQUniversity, Australia.

GPA: 6.61 or High-Distinction (7 = highest; 0 = lowest)

2015 Third year of Engineering of Information Technology

University of Atacama, Chile.

GPA: 6.1 or High- Distinction (7 = highest; 1 = lowest)

2011 to 2014 Common core Engineering and Science

University of Chile, Chile.

GPA: 6.1 or High- Distinction (7 = highest; 1 = lowest)

CERTIFICATES/LICENCES

General Construction Induction course/White Card course valid from 16.04.2016

NSW Volunteer Work With Children Card valid to 20.08.2021

ACHIEVEMENTS AND AWARDS

2016 CQUniversity Vice-Chancellor's Scholarship

2010 1st in class in Last Year High School, Chile

WORK EXPERIENCE

2017 to Current Warehouse Operator (Casual)

Programmed, Sydney.

- Organising freight packaging in DHL Global Forwarding Australia in the export warehouse.
- Managing the in/out of freight in the warehouse.
- Training new employees about the packaging process of the freight and the warehouse functionality.

2018 to Current Young Adult Advisor (Volunteer)

Sydney Harbour, The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day-saints

- Teaching financial and planning tools to adults between 20 to 26 to make goals and plan studies.
- Public speaking at chapels and teaching classes.

2017 **Night-shift Office Cleaner** (Part-time)

JIO Cleaner Service, Sydney.

• Organising the night shift and the performance.

2015 **Physic Student Tutor** (Part-time)

University of Atacama, Chile.

- Guide students to perform the experiments in a physic laboratory.
- Direct the classroom and forming student groups.
- Teaching Microsoft Office tools to the student to prepare a report.

2012 to 2014 **Religious Mission** (Volunteer)

Chile Mission, The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day-saints

- Door knocking and volunteer services, including working with disadvantaged community members for two years in the South of Chile.
- 9 months managing the finances of the organisation and expenses of more than 200 volunteers.
- Usage of the enterprise system of the organisation and Microsoft Office tools and Microsoft Access.

WORK SKILL MATRIX

Skill	Level	Experience
Website Design	Advance and Expert	HTML and XML at an advanced level from work and university experience. Bootstraps and CSS at an expert level from designing a website from work and university experience.
Application Development	Competent	Developing an Android application at Android Studio for the university experience.
Online Communication Skill	Expert	Communicate through email at voluntary with leaders in the USA. Expert Communication at work and university through emails, Skype and Zoom meetings.
Communication Skill	Expert	Volunteering at Religious Mission communicating and introducing myself to new people every day. Work and university experience by presenting and participating in meetings to resolve problems.
Website Performance	Competent	PHP and JavaScript at a competent level for university experience providing functionalities to websites. MySQL, SQLite and Derby DB at a competent level for university experience to communicate websites and application to databases.
Enterprise Application	Competent and Expert	Java EE at a competent level for university experience to develop enterprise application by Java Servlet, XHTML, JPA, Maven, Glassfish. Java programming language at an expert level for work and university experience developing software, application and websites.
Finances management	Competent	Managing finance at a competent level for a religious organisation monitoring budgets, expenses and payments of utilities and rents.
Microsoft Office Package	Expert	Microsoft Office tools at an expert level for work, university and voluntaries experience by using: Word, PowerPoint, Excel, Microsoft Project, Microsoft Access, and Outlook.
Programming Languages	Expert	Programming languages understanding at an expert level for work, university and independent experience. Programming languages are Java, Python, C#, SQL, JavaScript, and PHP.
Teamwork	Expert	Teamwork skills at an expert level for work and university experience to share responsibility, achieve goals and taking the initiative.
Leadership	Expert	Leadership skill at an expert level for work experience leading teams, making decisions and resolving problems with projects.

PROFESSIONAL AFFILIATIONS

2018 Golden Key International Honour Society Australia

HOBBIES AND INTEREST

Voluntary work: Serving part-time in a church community to serve other members and non-members of the organisation. Also, performing community services such as cleaning yards and reconstruction of houses project to benefit the community.

Astronomy: Watching the sky at night to understand the behaviour of the cosmos. Memorising stats, constellation and regularly going outdoor to watch the sky. Also, researching relevant astronomical phenomena and understating the astronomical calculations. Learning how the university work and the astronomical laws on it make me appreciate new experiences and knowledge.

Outdoor activities: snorkelling, swimming and playing tennis.

REFERENCES

Professional

Mr Claudio Aravena Export Warehouse Supervisor, DHL Global Forwarding Australia, Matraville, NSW 2036 Mobile: 0432 057 561

Email: claudio.aravena@dhl.com

Academic

Dr Jose Belinchon
Professor of Physics and Astronomy,
Natural Science Department,
University of Atacama,
Copiapo, Chile
Email: jose.belinchon@uda.cl

Professional

Mr Matthews Pinato Senior Manager, JIO Cleaner Service, Matraville, NSW 2036 Mobile: 0403 787 317

Email: julio.pinato@dpworld.com